Wen Chien Lee

- ♥ Taipei, Taiwan
- wenchien0213@gmail.com (preferred means of contact)
- +886 911 249 226

Over 3 years experiences in Apparel design and E-commerce UI/Flow design. More than 2 years experiences in website design (contractors platform) since 2016.

As a user interface designer, I can assist front-end engineer with html and CSS, and also help PM planning user journey .By observing user behavior and welcoming user feedbacks, I am inspired to provide better user experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ul Designer Dec 2016 - Now

- · Developing new RWD projects in UIUX, html5, CSS2, CSS3
- · Defining the design guideline of new projects
- · Planning UI flow and function map for new projects in collaboration with PM
- · Liaising with PM and engineers
- · Supporting old project in html and css
- · Sketch / Photoshop / Illustrator / Invision / Zeplin / Sublime / VScode / git

Web Designer Feb 2013 - Nov 2016

- · Designed the UI / html / CSS of the official website (desktop and mobile sites)
- · Planned official blog (RWD)
- · Created and operated Event event pages and activity banners
- · Supported SEO
- · Product photography

EDUCATION

Shih Chien University 2006 - 2010

Department of Fashion Design and Merchandising

Degree: Bachelor of Arts

Grade: Top 1%

AWARD

The 10th ITHELP Ironman Contest (2019)

Sharing IT-related articles which about IT for 30 consecutive days.

Asia Illustrations Annual Awards

Nominated the award with the "Latte Rabbit and Coffee Bear" series.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

Volunteer teacher 2018 - Now

Career sharing is towith junior high school's students.

Learning Git group 2018 – Now

Creator and operator of a Facebook group aboutwhich is learning git.

Illustrator 2017 - Now

Facebook Fan Pages: Latte Rabbit and Coffee Bear, released Had 1st set of LINEown line stickers in 2018.